Herman P. Wilhelm Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Herman P. Wilhelm Archives
1934-1965
ENTAR.001762
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
10
The archives of Herman P. Wilhelm.
Wilhelm, Herman Paul
Biographical Sketch
Herman P Wilhelm donated his collection to the Yale Peabody Museum.
Description of the Material
The archives of Herman P. Wilhelm, including correspondence and notebooks.
Connecticut; USA; Correspondence; Field notebooks; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Correspondence, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence recieved by Herman P. Wilhelm mostly concerning acquiring his collection.
  - Arnhold, F.R. EST. number of items = 5+., 1934; 001764
  - Baber, Donald L. EST. number of items = 3., 1953; 001765
  - Baker, Clement W. EST. number of items = 2., 1948-1950; 001766
  - Benesh, Bernard. EST. number of items = 1., 1958; 001767
  - Bower, H.M. EST. number of items = 5., 1960-1961; 001768
  - Brower, A.E. EST. number of items = 15+., 1944-1961; 001769
  - Brower, Lincoln P. EST. number of items = 2., 1951; 001770
  - Buchholz, Otto. EST. number of items = 1., 1946; 001772
  - Buell, Floyd A. EST. number of items = 1., 1933; 001771
  - Chermock, F.H. EST. number of items = 10+., 1935-1937; 001773
  - Concepcion, A.N. EST number of items =2., 1951; 001818
  - Denison, Harold. EST. number of items = 3., 1934; 001774
  - Dluhy, Eugene. EST. number of items = 40+., 1948-1962; 001775
  - Dos Passos, Cyril. EST. number of items = 1., 1948; 001776
  - Downey, Duke. EST. number of items = 20+., 1948-1963; 001777
  - Dunhoff, Stephen H. EST number of items = 2., 1962; 001778
  - Engel. Henry. EST number of items = 2., 1937; 001779
  - Forsyth, Lesley E. EST number of items = 5+., 1935; 001780
  - Frenchin, D.P. EST number of items = 1., 001781
  - Glanz, A. Butterfly World Supply House. EST number of items = 10+., 1944-1949; 001782
  - Grey, L.P. EST number of items = 10+., 1956-1960; 001783
  - Halbert, R. EST number of items = 1., 1961; 001784
  - Hayes, Joseph B. EST number of items = 1., 1956; 001785
  - Hellman, Geoffrey T. EST number of items = 1., 1959; 001786
  - Hensel, Henry. EST number of items = 1., 1961; 001793
  - Hessel, Sydney A. EST number of items = 5., 1957-1964; 001787
  - Hills, William. EST number of items =3., 1962; 001819
  - Hogue, Charles L. EST number of items = 1., 1951; 001788
  - Holley, F.E. EST number of items = 10., 1948-1951; 001789
  - Howe, William. EST number of items = 5., 1950; 001790
  - Jancik, Otto. EST number of items = 2., 1962; 001792
  - Jewett, Stanely. EST number of items = 2., 1934; 001791
  - Kaiser, Justus. EST number of items = 5., 1947; 001794
  - Kessler, F.D. EST number of items = 5., 1953; 001795
  - Kimball, Charles P. EST number of items = 5., 1958-1959; 001796
  - Kutis, John. EST number of items = 2., 1955; 001797
  - Mattoni, R. EST number of items = 1., 1949; 001798
  - Maynard, Elliot A. EST number of items = 3., 1940; 001799
  - Naumann, Fred. EST number of items = 3., 1958-1959; 001800
  - Osborne, Melville W. EST number of items = 10+., 1951-1958; 001801
  - Pease, Roger W. EST number of items = 1., 1959; 001802
  - Pulsifer, Bruce C. EST number of items = 1., 1962; 001803
  - Ragsdale, H.L. EST number of items = 3., 1952; 001804
  - Reinthal, Walfried J. EST number of items = 20+., 1954-1962; 001805
  - Remington, Charles Lee. EST number of items = 5+., 1955-1959; 001806
  - Ritterbush, Philip C. EST number of items = 5+., 1957; 001807
  - Roever, Kilian. EST number of items = 1., 1961; 001808
  - Rogers, W. P. EST number of items = 1., 1948; 001809
  - Rossie, John. EST number of items = 2., 1937; 001810
  - Sala, Frank P. EST number of items = 1., 1953; 001811
  - Smith, Eugene. EST number of items = 1., 1936; 001812
  - Smith, Richard. EST number of items = 2., 1955-1956; 001813
  - Unknown. EST number of items =5+., 001820
  - Vives Puigpelat, J. EST number of items =5+., 1959-1960; 001814
  - Wind, Robert G. EST number of items =3., 1950; 001815
  - Wyatt, Gerad R. EST number of items =1., 1958; 001816
  - Zappalorti, Micheal. EST number of items =1., 001817
- Notebooks, Series II
  Miscellaneous notebooks, some belong were kept by his wife Anna.
  - Miscellaneous. notebooks and diaries kept by Herman P. Wilhelm and his wife., 001823